Sanjar Hakimi

PROJEČT MANAGER, SCRUM MASTER, PRODUCT OWNER

Woodbridge, VA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Sanjar-Hakimi/91612dfa3e8187b6

Over fifteen years of managing and developing multimedia solutions in the area of website design and programming, including

Drupal development using Agile methodologies. Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Scrum Master

CVP, Inc - Fairfax, VA - April 2015 to Present

Industry: Government

Responsibility:

- Manage the team's Scrum framework and promote agile development.
- Served as the team's Accessibility Champion, promoting accessibility enhancements.
- Development on Drupal-based web applications for Center for Medicare Service
- Technologies utilized in role: Drupal 7, Amazon Web Service, JIRA, Cygwin, WinSCP, Red Hat Linux, Drupal, MySQL,

Apache, Selenium

Drupal Developer

Lockheed Martin - Arlington, VA - August 2014 to March 2015

Industry: Government

Responsibility:

- Development on Drupal-based web portal for GSA applications
- Technologies utilized in role: BRMS, Web Service, PHP SOAP library, WinSCP, PuTTY, Red Hat Linux, Drupal 7, MySQL,

Apache, AngularJS

Web Developer

Goldbelt Hawk - Newport News, VA - March 2012 to August 2014

Clients: White House, FEMA, Goldbelt HQ

Role/Title: Web Developer

Industry: Government, Commercial

Responsibility:

- Drupal development on gbhawk.com, serve.gov, nationalservice.gov, nationalserviceresources.gov
- Technologies utilized in role: WinSCP, Putty, Ubuntu Linux, Drupal, Photoshop, Dreamweaver, MySQL,
 Apache, Fiddler

Web Developer

Earth Resources Technology - Laurel, MD - July 2009 to March 2012

Industry: Government

Responsibility:

SharePoint 2007 administration, development and training of Intranet and public facing sites.

• Technologies utilized in role: SharePoint 2010, SharePoint Server 2007, SharePoint Designer, Visual Studio, StSadm.

Adobe Suite

Web Systems Manager

National Quality Forum - Washington, DC - February 2008 to July 2009

Industry: Healthcare Responsibility:

Administration of Siteorganic content management system, Ektron content management system and iMIS association

management administration

• Technologies utilized in role: Siteorganic, Ektron, iMIS, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, PowerPoint, ASP.NET, Acrobat, Bridge,

JavaScript, MS Access, MS Excel, XHTML, CSS, XML, MS Visio, Flash Video, SQL Server 2005

Web Developer

Flatter & Associates - Fredericksburg, VA - July 2007 to February 2008

Industry: US Military Responsibility:

- Development on Windows SharePoint Services 2003
- Technologies utilized in role: SharePoint Server 2003, FrontPage, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, PowerPoint, ASP, Illustrator,

JavaScript, MS Access, MS Excel, Captivate, XHTML, PHP, MySQL

Web Developer

InfoReliance - Fairfax, VA - September 2006 to July 2007

Industry: Government, US Marine Corp

Responsibility:

- Development on Windows SharePoint Services 2003
- Technologies utilized in role: SharePoint Server 2003, FrontPage, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, PowerPoint, ASP, Illustrator,

JavaScript, MS Access, MS Excel, Captivate, XHTML, PHP, MySQL

Information Technology Specialist

Montgomery County - Rockville, MD - April 2006 to September 2006

Industry: Government

Responsibility:

- Web manager in the Office of Cable and Communication Services
- Managed video streaming of Council's sessions
- Administer and develop public websites (Cable Office, Channel 6 and PEG Network)
- Technologies utilized in role: Pictron Video Gateway Media, Windows Media Encoder, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, InDesign,

PowerPoint, Flash, XML Markup, Web Edit Pro, Coldfusion, ASP, Acrobat, Outlook, Bridge, Illustrator, JavaScript,

Actionscript, MS Access, MS Excel, Captivate, XHTML, HTML, CSS

Multimedia Developer

Advance Concepts - Vienna, VA - June 2005 to December 2005

Industry: Conference Management

Responsibility:

- IT lead for on-site events, supervising A/V technicians
- Edited video projects for DVD, Web distribution
- Multimedia developer on various client projects
- Technologies utilized in role: XHTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, Dreamweaver, FrontPage, GoLive, Photoshop, Illustrator, Visio,

PowerPoint, Access, Excel, WebEx, Final Cut Pro, After Effects, Director, Fireworks, DVD Studio, Flash, Access, Excel,

Captivate

EDUCATION

Web Design and New Media

Academy of Art University - San Francisco, CA 2009 to 2014

Associate of Applied Science in Applied Science

Northern Virginia Community College - Annandale, VA 1993 to 1995

SKILLS

Web Development (10+ years), Project Management (10+ years)